<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Faster payments for creators. Paperchain is a wallet and card funded by your digital content revenues. Daily.</title>
    <link>https://paperchain.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Faster payments for creators. Paperchain is a wallet and card funded by your digital content revenues. Daily.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 16:51:15 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paperchain.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Paperchain, Centrifuge, Maker Foundation Perform World First, Real-Time Advance of $60,000 USD in Spotify Revenue Using Decentralized Finance</title>
      <link>https://paperchain.io/press/releases/paperchain-perform-world-first-real-time-spotify-advance-using-defi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 16:51:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paperchain.io/press/releases/paperchain-perform-world-first-real-time-spotify-advance-using-defi/</guid>
      <description>Paperchain, Centrifuge, Maker Foundation Perform World First, Real-Time Advance of $60,000 USD in Spotify Revenue Using Decentralized Finance 18 September 2019
 At DeFi Summit London, Paperchain and Centrifuge leveraged decentralized finance protocols to advance $60,000 USD in Spotify revenue to a Paperchain record label customer; While media consumption has shifted to streaming and on demand models, the revenue and payments process hasn’t changed; Revenue from a Spotify stream can take 3 months to reach a record label; 6 months to reach an artist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About us — Paperchain</title>
      <link>https://paperchain.io/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 16:51:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paperchain.io/about-us/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Australian founder Daniel Dewar to tackle $2.5bn in music royalty black boxes with music technology startup Paperchain</title>
      <link>https://paperchain.io/press/releases/daniel-dewar-tackle-royalty-black-boxes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 16:51:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paperchain.io/press/releases/daniel-dewar-tackle-royalty-black-boxes/</guid>
      <description>Australian founder Daniel Dewar to tackle $2.5bn in music royalty black boxes with music technology startup Paperchain 01 August 2017
 When a streaming service or performing rights organisation is unable to identify the rights owner to pay royalties to, unpaid royalties are held in “royalty black boxes” The global value of these royalty black boxes is estimated to be $2.5bn Paperchain has developed a product to connect rights owners to their unpaid royalties Australian founder Daniel Dewar is basing Paperchain out of London to focus on the large publishing and recording industry opportunities in the US, UK and Europe  London, UK &amp;ndash; Paperchain, a global music technology company, is aiming to solve the music industry’s problem of unpaid royalties by going after the growing amount of unidentified copyright owners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creator advances by Paperchain</title>
      <link>https://paperchain.io/creator-advances/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 16:51:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paperchain.io/creator-advances/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In the News — Paperchain</title>
      <link>https://paperchain.io/press/in-the-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 16:51:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paperchain.io/press/in-the-news/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian entrepreneur Rahul Rumalla to tackle $2.5bn in music royalty black boxes with music technology startup Paperchain</title>
      <link>https://paperchain.io/press/releases/rahul-rumalla-tackle-royalty-black-boxes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 16:51:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paperchain.io/press/releases/rahul-rumalla-tackle-royalty-black-boxes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;indian-entrepreneur-rahul-rumalla-to-tackle-25bn-in-music-royalty-black-boxes-with-music-technology-startup-paperchain&#34;&gt;Indian entrepreneur Rahul Rumalla to tackle $2.5bn in music royalty black boxes with music technology startup Paperchain&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;01 August 2017&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When a streaming service or performing rights organisation is unable to identify the rights owner to pay royalties to, unpaid royalties are held in “royalty black boxes”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The global value of these royalty black boxes is estimated to be $2.5bn&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paperchain has developed a product to connect rights owners to their unpaid royalties&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Indian entrepreneur Rahul Rumalla is basing Paperchain out of London to focus on the large publishing and recording industry opportunities in the US, UK and Europe&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>London-based startup Paperchain to tackle $2.5bn in music royalty black boxes from 46m NOI filings to US Copyright Office</title>
      <link>https://paperchain.io/press/releases/paperchain-tackle-royalty-black-boxes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 16:51:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paperchain.io/press/releases/paperchain-tackle-royalty-black-boxes/</guid>
      <description>London-based startup Paperchain to tackle $2.5bn in music royalty black boxes from 46m NOI filings to US Copyright Office 01 August 2017
 More than 46 million instances of unidentified songwriters or unknown copyright owner Notice of Intents (NOIs) digitally filed with the US Copyright Office by streaming services since April 2016 These are filed under the Notice of Intention to Obtain a Compulsory License - Section 115 clause in the US Copyright Act.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paperchain Card Service</title>
      <link>https://paperchain.io/terms-of-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 16:51:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paperchain.io/terms-of-use/</guid>
      <description>Welcome! We’re excited you have decided to use our platform and related card services, which we will refer to as “Services.”
These Terms of Service (which we’ll call “Terms”) should tell you everything you need to know, and everything we must tell you by law, regarding your initial use of our Services. These Terms are effective beginning when you sign up for our Service and end when your Service is terminated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paperchain Cardholder Agreement</title>
      <link>https://paperchain.io/cardholder-agreement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 16:51:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paperchain.io/cardholder-agreement/</guid>
      <description>IMPORTANT — PLEASE READ CAREFULLY
1. Terms and Conditions for the Paperchain Prepaid Visa® Card. This document is an agreement (&amp;ldquo;Agreement&amp;rdquo;) containing the terms and conditions that apply to the Paperchain Visa Card that has been issued to you by Celtic Bank pursuant to a license from Visa U.S.A. Inc. By accepting and/or using this Card, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions contained in this Agreement, as well as the Stripe Issuing Spend Card and Stripe Issuing Spend Card User Terms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paperchain for artists, creators &amp; managers</title>
      <link>https://paperchain.io/artists-creators-managers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 16:51:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paperchain.io/artists-creators-managers/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paperchain for record labels and distributors</title>
      <link>https://paperchain.io/labels-distributors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 16:51:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paperchain.io/labels-distributors/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paperchain founders taking part in the European Innovation Academy Extreme Entrepreneurship program in Portugal</title>
      <link>https://paperchain.io/press/releases/paperchain-european-innovation-academy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 16:51:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paperchain.io/press/releases/paperchain-european-innovation-academy/</guid>
      <description>Paperchain founders taking part in the European Innovation Academy Extreme Entrepreneurship program in Portugal 14 July 2017
London, UK &amp;ndash; The founders of Paperchain, the global music technology company solving the problem of unpaid royalties to music copyright owners, have been invited by the European Innovation Academy to take part in its Extreme Entrepreneurship program in Portugal throughout July and August.
The three week offers founders a mentor network to build key industry relationships to quickly iterate and deliver a product that can be taken to market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paperchain invited to the Wallifornia Music Tech Summit Acceleration &amp; Invest Program</title>
      <link>https://paperchain.io/press/releases/paperchain-wallifornia-music-tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 16:51:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paperchain.io/press/releases/paperchain-wallifornia-music-tech/</guid>
      <description>Paperchain invited to the Wallifornia Music Tech Summit Acceleration &amp;amp; Invest Program 16 June 2017
Valencia, Spain &amp;ndash; Paperchain, the global music technology company providing data validation services to music copyright owners, has been invited by Wallifornia MusicTech to take part in its Acceleration &amp;amp; Invest Program, happening July 3 - 7 in Liege, Belgium.
The program is held just before the Les Ardentes Festival and is carried out by Leansquare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paperchain Privacy Request Form</title>
      <link>https://paperchain.io/privacy-request-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 16:51:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paperchain.io/privacy-request-form/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Press releases — Paperchain</title>
      <link>https://paperchain.io/press/releases/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 16:51:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paperchain.io/press/releases/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Press — Paperchain</title>
      <link>https://paperchain.io/press/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 16:51:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paperchain.io/press/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you, from the Paperchain team</title>
      <link>https://paperchain.io/creator-form-submit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 16:51:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paperchain.io/creator-form-submit/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you, from the Paperchain team</title>
      <link>https://paperchain.io/form-submit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 16:51:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paperchain.io/form-submit/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you, from the Paperchain team</title>
      <link>https://paperchain.io/thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 16:51:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paperchain.io/thank-you/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uh oh - you&#39;re hit the Paperchain 404 page</title>
      <link>https://paperchain.io/404/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 16:51:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paperchain.io/404/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-sign Consent — Paperchain</title>
      <link>https://paperchain.io/esign-consent/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 16:51:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paperchain.io/esign-consent/</guid>
      <description>ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS AGREEMENT This E-sign Disclosure and Consent (“E-sign Consent”) applies to all Records and Communications for services provided on the Paperchain website and mobile application. “Records and Communications” includes all communications and mobile application notifications related to the accounts issued by Evolve Bank and Stripe Payments Company through Paperchain Inc., dba Paperchain, including the services described in the Terms of Use (https://paperchain.io/terms-of-use) as well as any modification or amendments hereto; any policies, notices or disclosures; and all other information that we may be required to provide to you in writing by law.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy — Paperchain</title>
      <link>https://paperchain.io/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 16:51:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paperchain.io/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Last updated June 07, 2021 We take privacy seriously.
If you visit any of Paperchain websites, download or use the Paperchain App or our Services, Paperchain will ask for, collect, and store personal information about you (your “Personal Data”). We would not be able to provide our Services to you without the Personal Data you provide us, which is why we want you to know that we take our responsibility to protect your Personal Data very seriously.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
